Finding Aid for the The Francis Robinson Collection
Special Collections and University Archives
- (The File Description)
  - Enrico Caruso
    - Address List for Complimentary Copies (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - Caruso - Telecasts (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - Robinson and Publisher (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - Robinson and Caruso Interest (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - Cover design for FR's Book (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - Caruso - Radio Broadcast Scripts (Box 204, Folder 6)
    - Texts and Drafts of Speeches, Articles, Record Notes (Box 204, Folder 7)
    - Clippings about Robinson and his Caruso (Box 204, Folder 8)
    - Drafts for Caruso (Box 204, Folder 9)
    - FR's Research Notes for Caruso (Box 204, Folder 10)
    - FR in Prints on Caruso (Box 204, Folder 11)
    - Reviews of Caruso (Box 204, Folder 12)
    - Book Announcements, Catalogues: Caruso (Box 204, Folder 13)
    - Publicity Material: Caruso (Box 204, Folder 14)
  - Enrico Caruso
    - Appreciation for FR's Book - Abbott - Brunie (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - Appreciation for FR's Book - Buell - Curry (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - Appreciation for FR's Book - Daniel - Fahlbusch (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - Appreciation for FR's Book - Farrar - Gillmore (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - Appreciation for FR's Book - Gimma - Hyman (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - Appreciation for FR's Book - Ietti - Losar (Box 205, Folder 6)
    - Appreciation for FR's Book - Lucrer - Maxwell (Box 205, Folder 7)
    - Appreciation for FR's Book - Mazzarella - Polacco (Box 205, Folder 8)
    - Appreciation for FR's Book - Pons - Saunders (Box 205, Folder 9)
    - Appreciation for FR's Book - Scarpato - Swift (Box 205, Folder 10)
    - Appreciation for FR's Book - Taubman - Zwed (Box 205, Folder 11)
    - Sources and Credits for FR's Book - Allan - Ivanian (Box 205, Folder 12)
    - Sources and Credits for FR's Book - Kapp - Nunez (Box 205, Folder 13)
    - Sources and Credits for FR's Book - O'Farrill - Saunders (Box 205, Folder 14)
    - Sources and Credits for FR's Book - Schlesinger - Shoemarer (Box 205, Folder 15)
    - Sources and Credits for FR's Book - Simonelli - Stiedry (Box 205, Folder 16)
    - Sources and Credits for FR's Book - Stracciali - Zirato (Box 205, Folder 17)
  - Enrico Caruso
    - Caruso's Checkbook (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Caruso's Stamps (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - Contract between Caruso and Jose del Rivers (Box 206, Folder 3)
    - Hotel Knickerbocker Envelope with Caruso's Notes (Box 206, Folder 4)
  - Robinson Scrapbook Collection
    - European Photographs 1901, No. 1 (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - European Photographs 1901, No. 2 (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - Composers' Scrapbook (Box 207, Folder 3)
  - Robinson Scrapbook Collection
    - Scrapbook on Concerts (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook on Concerts (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook Pages on Singers (Box 208, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook Pages on Singers (Box 208, Folder 4)
  - Registers - Misc.
    - Zirato Correspondence Collection Register (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - Caruso Collection Register (Box 209, Folder 2)
    - Dance Collection Register (Box 209, Folder 3)
    - Theatre Collection Register (Box 209, Folder 4)
    - Artifacts and Pictures Collection Register (Box 209, Folder 5)
    - Autograph Collection Register (Box 209, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence Collection Register (Box 209, Folder 7)
    - Farrer Correspondence Collection Register (Box 209, Folder 8)
    - Music Collection Register (Box 209, Folder 9)
    - Naff Collection Register (Box 209, Folder 10)
    - Naff Correspondence Register (Box 209, Folder 11)
    - Opera Collection Register (Box 209, Folder 12)
    - Recording Collection Register (Box 209, Folder 13)
    - Robinson Personal Collection Register (Box 209, Folder 14)
  - Misc. Materials
  - Misc. Materials
  - Misc. Materials
  - Misc. Frog rams
    - MET Opera House Programs and Dinner Menus (Box 213)
  - Bell Telephone Orchestra
    - Bell Telephone Hour - Numbered Series (Box 209)